This is Trigun.
guitar solo
I don't know.
I picked up my first gun at
the age of seven and I shot.
I remember how strangely easy
it was to pull the trigger.
I actually laughed.
Because that one shot was all it took to
finally silence that
sickening piece of garbage
who had the nerve to
call himself my guardian.
It was that simple.
And so, I was free.
Yes, tomorrow things would be different.
Tomorrow.
As much as I wanted to believe,
it only went from bad to worse.
A vicious cycle.
Life is like an incessant
series of problems.
All seem difficult, with
brutal choices and a time.
The single worst thing we
can do is to make no choice
while we're waiting for
the answer to come to us.
We must make the best
decision in a split second.
We are nothing like God.
Not only are our powers limited,
we sometimes are driven to
become the devil himself.
I didn't want other kids to grow up
like me, so I started my own orphanage.
It was gratifying work.
I was actually doing something
for the good of others.
It was my place of peace and happiness.
Yet sometimes, I still think to myself,
there's no place worse than this planet.
It's horrible here.
I don't know what to do,
I don't know what to do.
I don't understand you, Knives.
How can you enjoy this?
Ah, shit.
This thing's filthy.
You're wrong!
He wasn't gonna shoot me!
Please, please don't look at me like that.
There are extenuating
circumstances you don't understand.
You still need some work.
It's not healthy to hesitate,
Because every time you do you wear
down a little more of your life.
I'm sure I told you that before haven't I?
Why have you come here?
Apparently you've lost some weight.
Why Nicholas?
I've been traveling
with a real troublemaker
It's not wise to drown
in each other's pain.
It's time for you to kill this man now
But Knives specifically told
me to bring him back alive.
The order was not to destroy him
I'm afraid that order has been retracted.
What about the money?
Don't worry It will be
paid as promised follow
through with your mission
and I guarantee the lives
of your precious December
orphan children upon
the holy name of the chapel
of the gung-ho guns and
As of now you too my friend
are also a gung-ho gun
Deal with the situation as instructed,
and you will inherit my title.
The way he looked at me, it was as
though he was the one who killed the kid.
Damn it, I'll take the blame.
Hit me if you need to.
Then, maybe at least I can... Mr. Priest?
Oh, good.
I was hoping I'd find you here.
I thought you might be hungry, so
Meryl and I made you sandwiches,
and I'd be very happy if you'd eat them.
Oh, yeah, and you take
your coffee black, right?
Why haven't you said anything
anything about the kid?
I killed the other day.
Oh
Oh, I just don't know what to say.
I'm so confused
Because what you said
was right and what mr.
Vash said was true, too.
I I don't like it when people have to die.
What would you have done?
I don't know, really.
That's not good enough!
I don't understand him.
Even in such an impossible situation,
he keeps saying that nobody had to die.
How can he believe that?
That's the way Mr.
Vash has always been.
I know because I've watched
him for a long time.
He's lived by that rule his whole life.
It's very important to him.
Thou shalt not kill, remember?
What the hell kind of
church man are you anyway?
Come on!
I've lived my life very differently from
him, and I guess I have to accept that.
I was supposed to guide him.
I was ordered to protect him.
It was my job to be there for him.
But the mission, the obligation,
it doesn't matter anymore.
I honestly wanted to save him,
even if it meant killing a child.
I actually wanted to save him.
I had no alternative.
I had to choose one or the other.
It's so strange.
Where did I go wrong?
I've always chosen the
right path, haven't I?
Ah, thank you.
You're so kind.
You need your strength.
Please eat the sandwiches.
Will you please eat them with me?
Millie's so late getting back to her room.
I don't know.
What should I do?
What should I say to him?
Rem.
Are you leaving without saying goodbye?
I shouldn't have hit you the other day.
You didn't deserve it.
I'm really sorry.
It's all right.
Maybe there was a way out of that problem.
Maybe what we should have done
would have been something.
Like shut up.
That's enough.
Our lives are too different.
Vash you and I were
destined to come to this.
It's part of who I am.
Long ago we started a
quick draw tournament.
We're going to settle it
at last right here and now.
Why at this time?
If I tell you, will
you agree to die? Draw.
Draw.
Okay.
I'll do that for you.
But in return, will you
do something for me?
Yeah. What?
When this is all over and I'm dead,
you won't ever shoot anyone again.
When this is over and I'm dead,
you don't ever shoot anyone again.
Do you actually expect me to become
a living target like you are?
Alright, so how do you plan to
get out of this predicament, huh?
I don't know.
Then answer me one thing.
You're obviously going after Knives.
What do you intend to
do once you find him?
Many years ago, he stole someone
who was very important to me.
So you want revenge?
I don't know.
I really don't know.
I see.
So that's how you live.
That's how you choose to live.
You know what?
You're an expert at
pissing me off. Amazing.
Hey, Wolfwood.
Take cover!
Fire that!
It must be Kane.
He's probably sniping from
the outskirts of town.
If we don't do something
now, he will hit his target.
And he's not alone. What?
Why don't you go after Kane?
You shouldn't have any
problem finding him.
The other one's mine.
By the way, I only know
you as the Stampede.
I think you can at least
tell me your real name.
No way.
I'm not gonna tell you just so you
can go out and get killed today.
No, don't be stupid. Tell me.
Between you and me?
My name's irrelevant.
Time to get back to business, Vash.
Wolfwood, why?
No, doesn't matter.
Mr. Walpole!
I hear gunfire!
Millie, what are you doing here?
I'm staying here, Merrill.
He told me to stay here.
He made me promise.
So I'm not moving until he comes back.
Alcohol?
He let me in here.
The only clues I had were
the lag time between rifle
reports and my rough calculations
of the angles on impact.
I had a hard time finding you.
Well, gee, now, since your gun's gone
to pieces, why don't you head on home?
It's too hot out here.
Great, I'm glad you're seeing it my way.
Where?
Where will he attack from?
Oh, shit!
So now what's the best choice?
Tell me.
Is this good enough?
Is it?
I'm done.
That's gonna be it for me.
Now that's tasty!
This is a huge disappointment to me.
I can't believe you'd so easily waste
the ten years of training I gave you.
Actually, it wasn't wasted at all.
I've used everything you've taught me.
I just decided to do things
a little differently.
May you go with God's protection?
Oh yeah, and thanks for the app.
What's wrong I failed I failed to
save someone again man is born a mortal
being and we all make mistakes it's
part of the game just be more careful
the next time it's hard for me to
accept making mistakes like this then
you can choose to suffer that's also
a part of the experience of mortal
Oh yeah, mortal.
By the way, Knives is in Dimitri.
What did you say?
I never told you anything about Knives.
How did you know that?
I hope you don't mind
me barging in like this.
In spite of the profession I've chosen,
I've never actually made
a confession before.
It's these times we live in.
I did what it took to protect
the children at any cost.
That's how I always justified my actions.
I took many people's lives.
All that time, believing
there was no other way.
My sins are so heavy.
Too heavy.
Too heavy to ever atone for.
And yet, somehow I feel happy.
At peace with myself today.
It really can be done.
Once you stop to think about it, there
are plenty of ways to save everyone.
Why didn't I ever listen to him?
Why didn't I see that
before it was too late?
That tastes good.
You know cigarettes are
bad for the baby, darling?
I'm sorry, honey.
If I am reincarnated, I'd like to
live somewhere where life is easier!
Somewhere with nothing but peaceful days.
Somewhere with no stealing.
No killing.
Eden?
In Eden?
I could live happily
with him, and the girls.
I'm not ready yet.
There's still so much left to be done.
I want to stay with them.
I don't want to die.
I'm a man.
Was everything I did in my life a mistake?
Would I be wrong now to
ask for your forgiveness?
I did not want to die this way!
I don't know.
The blue sky in the middle of the
sky, the wind is in the future.
The day of the day of the day,
the light is in the future.
But,
I'll just leave you alone.
I'll just
leave you alone.
If you have a right hand and a hand!
If you have a right hand!
Repeated tragedies, repeated pain,
the wishes of a man are so
strong and yet so frail and weak.
To live,
to stay alive, who would have known that
survival was this hard, this painful?
I must choose.
I must make the choice.
In the moment that intertwines life and
death, can I choose to remain a human?